so welcome to this intelligent tricks
所以欢迎来到这个聪明的把戏
first we're going to start with
首先，我们将从
navigating to type right so commando I
导航键入正确的，所以突击队我
go to type you'll know this I can write
输入您可以知道的内容，我会写
for example operation operation time
例如操作操作时间
interval and it takes me to operation
间隔，这需要我进行操作
time interval right that's nothing new
时间间隔没什么新鲜的
oti also does the same thing so camel
奥蒂也做同样的事情，所以骆驼
kinks completion takes me exactly to the
纠结完成将我带到
to the to the type without me having to
无需我就可以
type all of that things and this works
键入所有这些东西，这有效
exactly the same way for files so shift
完全相同的文件转移方式
command oh it's the same thing and if I
命令哦，是同一回事，如果我
write scheduler it takes me to files I
编写调度程序，它将我带到我的文件
can also do file paths so for example I
也可以做文件路径，例如
could do rx and that would show me all
可以做RX，那会告诉我所有
of the folders right so you can also not
正确的文件夹，所以您也不能
only navigate to files you can also
只导航到您也可以
navigate to folders now also what you
现在导航到文件夹
can do is if you go to a file for
可以做的是，如果您转到文件
example you could do scheduler and then
例如你可以做调度程序，然后
write for T and what that does as you
为T写东西，你会做什么
can imagine is take you to line 40 of
可以想象是带您到40号线
that file okay so you can do that
那个文件好吧，所以你可以这样做
directly symbol lookup so that's type
直接查找符号，以便输入
lookup and file lookup symbol lookup is
查找和文件查找符号查找是
is also efficient because it allows you
也很有效，因为它可以让您
to basically search for symbol across
基本搜索符号
the entire solution right so I can do
完整的解决方案，所以我可以做
for instance some float or I could do
例如一些浮动或我可以做
index and that will basically show me
索引，这基本上会告诉我
all of the different indexes that exist
存在的所有不同索引
anywhere inside my entire project which
我整个项目中的任何地方
is a pain a pain in the in the rear so
是后方的痛苦
what happens if I want to go to some
如果我想去一​​些会发生什么
float but I know more or less where in
浮动，但我或多或少知道
what namespace it is you can do
您可以做什么命名空间
namespace filtering so you can do for
命名空间过滤，因此您可以
example OSC some float and that will
例如OSC一些浮动，那将
take me to the type Oh s T which is
带我去看哦，是
operation some test and then to the met
操作一些测试然后到遇到
symbol only inside that so you can
仅在其中包含符号，以便您可以
actually filter by namespace
实际上按名称空间过滤
double-shift gives you search everywhere
双班让您到处搜索
you know this so search everywhere is
你知道这个，所以到处搜索
basically search for anything everywhere
基本上到处搜索任何东西
absolutely anything so I could do
绝对有什么我可以做的
operation take time whatever and it will
操作需要时间，无论如何，它将
show me a type I can tap and go - well
给我看看我可以轻按的类型-好
that's file right I can tab go to
那是文件的权利，我可以转到
classes tab go to more tab again go to
类别标签，再转到更多标签，转到
files and go through all of the
文件，并通过所有
different sections but it searches not
不同的部分，但不会搜索
only for types and files etc it searches
仅搜索类型和文件等
anything so things that you don't know
任何你不知道的东西
where they are
他们在哪里
you can basically look them up in search
您基本上可以在搜索中查找它们
everywhere so one of the things that you
到处都是，所以你的一件事
were mentioning is on the project you
被提到是在你的项目上
can see that as I change you see that it
可以看到，随着我的改变，你看到了
syncs here
在这里同步
now you can make this sink doesn't
现在你可以使这个水槽不
actually but it can sink so you can
实际上，但是它可以下沉，所以您可以
select Auto scroll to source or Auto
选择自动滚动到源或自动
scroll from source and basically what
从源滚动，基本上是什么
this means is that when I change the
这就是说，当我改变
source file it will scroll for me on the
源文件，它将为我滚动
project window when I change from the
当我从
project window to the source file it
项目窗口到源文件吧
will also change I don't have auto
也会改变我没有自动
scroll to source enabled I don't really
滚动到启用源，我不是真的
like it I do have auto scroll from
喜欢它，我确实有自动滚动
source so I always know where I am in
源，所以我总是知道我在哪里
the project window when I navigate to a
当我导航到项目窗口时
different file a lot of times especially
特别是很多不同的文件
people that come from editors they come
来自编辑的人
to intelligent like how the hell am I
聪明到我该死的样子
going to write code in that you don't
你不会写代码
write there's no real estate there you
写那里没有房地产
have to hide all the windows ok and you
必须隐藏所有窗户，然后您
can hide all the windows with a quick
可以快速隐藏所有窗户
shortcut shift command f12 and that
快捷键移位命令f12和那个
basically goes back to what you had and
基本上回到你曾经拥有的
what you didn't have and then you can
你没有的东西然后你可以
also hide these icons here you see when
也将这些图标隐藏在此处
I do shift command f12 this panels are
我做shift命令f12这个面板是
still available I can hide these and
仍然可用，我可以隐藏这些
they're gone as well right and then if I
他们也没事了，如果我
want to go back to the previous mode I
想回到以前的模式
was easy to get in and out I could do
我可以轻松进出
double click on the command key and also
双击命令键，然后
get the windows back let go and lose
把窗户找回来，放手，输掉
them if you don't like that what you can
他们，如果你不喜欢那你可以
also do is enter what we call
也要做的就是输入我们所说的
distraction-free mode which basically
无干扰模式
gets rid of absolutely everything and
摆脱一切，
you just get the editor ok you can still
你只要让编辑器好就可以了
access stuff but otherwise everything
访问的东西，但其他一切
else is gone how do you select code in
否则，您如何选择代码
IntelliJ so on Mac what you do is you
IntelliJ，因此在Mac上您所要做的就是
press alt up and that selects the word
向上按alt，然后选择单词
and that's this is context-aware
这就是上下文感知
so now it selects the line and then it
所以现在选择线，然后
will select the method and then the
将选择方法，然后
class and then the entire auto class and
类，然后是整个汽车课，
then the entire package right and you
然后整个包装就对了
could shrink as well if you want to move
如果想移动也可以缩小
code you don't do a cut and paste right
您没有正确剪切和粘贴的代码
you actually use the functionality we
您实际上使用了我们的功能
have to move code around and place it in
必须四处移动代码并将其放入
places that are awful and won't compile
糟糕且无法编译的地方
if you want to delete a line just press
如果要删除一行，只需按
ctrl Y if you want to duplicate it
Ctrl Y如果您要复制它
around press ctrl D ok we also
左右按ctrl D确认，我们也
introduced another thing in IntelliJ
在IntelliJ中介绍了另一件事
which is a support for multiple cursors
这是对多个游标的支持
so I can place the cursor here and then
所以我可以把光标放在这里
I can press another cursor here and I
我可以在这里按下另一个光标
can press another cursor here and I can
可以在这里按下另一个光标，我可以
mess things up really badly ok
搞砸了，真的很不好
ah now don't please use this for
啊，现在不要用这个
refactoring don't write there are many
重构不写有很多
built-in refactoring tools but sometimes
内置重构工具，但有时
you need multiple cursors ok so look at
您需要多个光标，所以请看一下
this this is horrible code right that
这是可怕的代码
really looks horrible and if I just want
看起来真的很恐怖，如果我只是想
to get the indentation right what I can
使缩进正确我可以
do is basically just select that and
基本上就是选择
then hit ctrl alt I to get the initation
然后按ctrl alt我得到启发
done if I want to reformat the entire
如果我想重新格式化整个
code so I could just do you know be
代码，这样我就可以知道
anywhere and then just to out command l
任何地方，然后只是出命令l
and reformat the entire code so again
然后重新格式化整个代码
don't spend too much time
不要花太多时间
reformat in code manually how many of
在代码中手动重新格式化多少个
you use language injections in IntelliJ
您在IntelliJ中使用语言注入
so what you can do here is you can say
所以你可以在这里说
I'll tenter and inject language and say
我会拉扯并注入语言然后说
JSON and now that string IntelliJ
JSON和现在的字符串IntelliJ
interprets it as JSON you can also do
将其解释为JSON也可以
regular expressions so let me go and say
正则表达式，让我说
check visa so here for example I have
检查签证，所以在这里我有
regular expressions but for IntelliJ
正则表达式，但适用于IntelliJ
this is just a string I can just say
这只是一个字符串，我只能说
inject language reference regular
注入语言参考规则
expression and now it will interpret
表达，现在它将解释
that as regular expression and then I
作为正则表达式，然后我
can also do check regular expression
也可以检查正则表达式
right so if I do that for instance or I
对，所以如果我这样做，或者我
can say it so this is a typical visa
可以这样说，这是典型的签证
card that has to start with 4 so if I
卡必须以4开头，所以如果我
put a 4 there it validates it if I add
如果我在其中放一个4，它将验证它
another digit it doesn't ok so here's a
另一个数字不正确，所以这是一个
buffer new reader and let me show you
缓冲新读者，让我告诉你
how you could basically do this if you
如果您基本上可以做到这一点
say bufferedreader reader equals new and
说bufferedreader reader等于new和
now get completion and that gives you
现在完成，这给你
basically everything there is right you
基本上一切都对你
don't use completion as much you should
不要过多使用完成功能
use smart completion smart completion is
使用智能完成智能完成是
going to limit it down to what actually
将其限制在实际范围内
makes sense
说得通
yeah if I have a bufferedreader only
是的，如果我只有缓冲读取器
certain things I can create instances
我可以创建实例的某些东西
off right and also oh this is already
对了，哦，这已经是
done but I'll remove this for you so
完成，但我会为您删除
that you can see make sure that when you
您可以确保在您
do for example file new reader often
例如经常归档新读者
also people lose this and they're like
人们也会失去这个，他们就像
oh how do I get access to that
哦，我如何获得它
information
信息
you don't delete this and do that again
您不删除它，然后再做一次
you can press command P to get parameter
您可以按命令P获取参数
info right and in fact here also what
信息权，实际上这里也是
you could do is well now I'll show that
你可以做的很好，现在我会告诉你
and so far reader
到目前为止，读者
so I say abc.txt that gives you alt
所以我说abc.txt可以让您
enter to add math except ssin handler to
输入以将除ssin处理程序以外的数学添加到
it so to kind of let IntelliJ work the
这样就可以让IntelliJ工作
completion for you okay
为你完成好吗
you can do doubles or double or second
你可以做双打或双打或秒
completion so for instance let's say I
完成，例如，假设我
have a string lines I could do reader
有一个我可以做的字符串
and if I invoke it again it will say
如果我再次调用它，它将说
reader dot read line which you wouldn't
读者点读行，您不会
do like that but anyway it allows you to
那样做，但无论如何，它允许您
basically chain methods and smartly
基本上是连锁方法
allow you to do second completion so
让你做第二次完成
that's invoking the same completion you
调用相同的完成
just invoke invoke it a second time
只是调用第二次
what else hippie completion so how many
还有什么嬉皮完成了多少
of you have heard of hippie completion
你们当中有听说过嬉皮完成
right hippie completion if I type T and
如果我输入T和
then press hippie completion it will
然后按嬉皮完成它会
loop through all of the things that
遍历所有的事情
match that T right
正确匹配T
so if I write teller it basically is
所以如果我写出纳员基本上是
going to do the same thing right it's
要做同样的事情吧
going to go through the each of the
将要经历的每个
different ones and and that's with alt /
不同的，这就是alt /
and now there's also another thing that
现在还有另一件事
we introduced which is called postfix
我们介绍了称为后缀
completion so for instance let's go
完成，例如，让我们走
ahead and create a person a person
领先并创造一个人
person which you could do with introduce
可以介绍的人
variable I know so let's say I just did
我知道变量，所以说我刚刚
if person equals new whatever but I
如果人等于新事物，除了我
forgot to do the if person is not do
如果人不做，就忘记做
this so post fit completion allows me to
这样贴合完成后，我就可以
call it in reverse so I can just say not
叫它相反，所以我只能说不
null and then call it in reverse did you
null，然后反向调用它吗
see that lot of these things are also
看到这些东西很多
available for different languages so for
适用于不同的语言，因此
instance I can go to Emmet here and this
实例我可以在这里去Emmet
is HTML I could say for example I have a
是HTML我可以说，例如，我有一个
paragraph here we also have already now
这里的段落我们现在也已经
it automatically changes so you don't
它会自动更改，因此您无需
have to do that but if I say for
必须这样做，但是如果我说
instance I'm going to wrap this Dib
实例我要包装这个Dib
inside a div I can select this div and
在div内，我可以选择该div，
then also invoke surround template and
然后还调用环绕声模板并
say surround it with another div so and
说用另一个div包围它，然后
a lot of these functionalities working
这些功能很多
in different places in in HTML of course
当然在HTML中的不同地方
we also have image how many of you use M
我们也有图像你们中有多少人使用M
it right so if I want to do for example
没错，所以如果我想做例如
UL and then Li what I can do is just
UL然后Li我能做的只是
press ctrl D a bunch of times or I can
多次按ctrl D或
use what's called like the CSS
使用所谓的CSS
completion so let's say I want a div and
完成，所以假设我要一个div和
I call it my dear and then inside this I
我称其为亲爱的，然后在其中
have ul and then I have li times 5 hit
有ul然后我有li次5次
tab and I get that
标签，我明白了
same thing outputted now let me switch
现在输出的相同的东西让我切换
over and show you a little bit of like
结束，给你一点点像
navigation analysis so for example if I
导航分析，例如，如果我
go to operation a time interval from
从以下时间间隔开始运行
here I can for instance go to command B
例如，在这里我可以转到命令B
or command Q and that will take me to
或命令Q，这将带我到
the super method etc then let's say for
超级方法等，然后让我们说
instance I'm I don't know let's go up
我不知道让我们走
here and observable right so I'll
在这里，可以观察到的权利，所以我会
command B that will give me all of the
命令B会给我所有的
different implementations observable
可观察到的不同实现
again here on all the windows basically
再次在这里基本上在所有窗户上
you can search in IntelliJ you don't
您可以在IntelliJ中搜索
have to do any manual scrolling and you
必须做任何手动滚动，你
know there's a lot of different ways to
知道有很多不同的方法
navigate back and forth so you can go to
来回导航，以便您可以转到
superclass you can go to the type class
你可以去类型类的超类
etc so in observable for instance
以此类推，例如
there's also something that people
还有一些人
really I find that they use which is the
真的，我发现他们使用的是
type hierarchy so that gives you a
键入层次结构，以便为您提供
hierarchy of the actual type if you go
实际类型的层次结构
to a method for instance let's go to
例如，让我们转到
lift on the method you can also get type
提起您也可以输入的方法
hierarchy which is a shift command H so
层次结构，它是移位命令H so
that gives you the same thing but for
这给你同样的事情，但是
method hierarchies okay sometimes when
方法层次结构有时还可以
you're in the actual a file you can
您在实际的文件中可以
press command f12 to give you a a pop-up
按命令f12给您一个弹出窗口
of the structure right which is a which
的结构权是
is a floating thing so I can say for
是一个浮动的东西，所以我可以说
instance long count and go directly to
实例长计数并直接转到
that without having to do the symbol
不必做符号
lookup this thing here is very annoying
在这里查找这个东西很烦人
you see this navigation bar it's great
您会看到这个导航栏，很棒
because I can select it and I can
因为我可以选择它，所以我可以
actually create new files and everything
实际上创建新文件
but again it takes up valuable state
但是它又占据了宝贵的状态
space so what you do is you switch it
空间，所以您要做的就是切换它
off and if you ever want it just invoke
关闭，如果您愿意，只需调用
it and then you can just invoke it from
它，然后您可以从中调用它
here and from there you can continue to
在这里和那里，您可以继续
create files and everything ok
创建文件，一切正常